Gu Chengze, I won't sign
I've waited so long for this wedding
Mingyao
Don't embarrass everyone
I've waited so long
Just for them to force me out together
Mingyao, there are so many guests today
Stop making a scene
Sign it
and don't embarrass both families
Sister, if you don't want to
I can return the ring
Yurou, this is not your fault
Su Mingyao
Don't lose your last shred of dignity
It turns out even if I refuse
No one will stand by my side
I refused to step down
But they still
Left me all alone
If I could do it all over again
But seriously, breaking off
the engagement on the spot
The ring is already on
someone else's finger
This time
I won't let them control my life again
Su Mingyao, sign it
I am reborn
Back to three years ago
Back to the day
I'm supposed to marry Fu Chenzhou
Brother Chengze
My sister must be so sad
Yurou, you're just too kind
What are you laughing at
At my terrible taste in the past
Mingyao, there are so many guests today
Stop making a scene
Sign it, you're the older sister
Let Yurou have this
Sister, maybe
I should return the ring to you
I'm marrying Yurou for
the future of both families
Sign it so everyone can save face
Sister
Thank you for letting me
and Brother Chengze be together
No need to thank me
The trash I don't want
You can just keep it
Su Mingyao, what did you write